and welcome to another installment of
欢迎来到另一期
spring tips and this installment we're
春天的技巧，这是我们的分期付款
going to look at spring tool suite for
来看看 spring tool suite
now there's a lot of new features in
现在有很多新功能
spring tool suite 4 and we're gonna
spring tool suite 4，我们将
focus on just a few of them we're gonna
只专注于其中的一些
launch the project here now keep in mind
现在开始在这里启动项目
this is a new release it's not GA yet
这是一个新版本，不是GA
Thea first the final release will be
Thea首先，最终版本将是
sometime next year I hope in the first
我希望明年的某个时候
half or so of next year so there's a lot
明年下半年左右，所以有很多
of great things already here and we can
伟大的事物已经在这里，我们可以
look forward to a lot more as as we
我们期待着更多
march towards the final release so I've
迈向最终版本，所以我已经
opened up spring tool suite for here and
在这里打开了 spring tool suite
we're gonna put a new project you know
我们要把一个新的项目，你知道
as usual gonna create a brand new
像往常一样会创造一个全新的
project give it a second here to
项目在这里给它第二次
stabilize there we go now new start tur
稳定在那里，我们现在开始新的开始
project good and we're gonna put a new
项目很好，我们要放一个新的
project just a regular old maven and a
只是一个普通的老专家和一个项目
Java project hit next I'll use the web
下一个Java项目，我将在网上使用
support I'll use h2 I'll use the
支持，我将使用h2
configuration property support and we'll
配置属性支持，我们将
use dev tools for live reloading and
使用开发工具进行实时重载和
we'll use what else do want you I guess
我想我们会用别的想要你的东西
that's a h2 web support JPA that'll be
这是H2网络支持JPA
fine actually we don't need JP we don't
很好，实际上我们不需要JP，我们不需要
need h2 in this case it's a very simple
在这种情况下需要h2非常简单
example and that I think is enough
例子，我认为就足够了
actuator of course for observability and
当然具有可观察性的执行器
for operational concerns we'll add that
出于运营方面的考虑，我们将添加
as well and we're gonna hit next and
以及，我们接下来要点击
that'll generate a new project that will
这将生成一个新项目，
then bring into our ID so again this is
然后带入我们的ID，这又是
very convenient we could have gone to
非常方便，我们本可以去
start that spring that I own and then
从我拥有的那个春天开始，然后
download the zip file and unzip it and
下载zip文件并解压缩，然后
then you know went to file import and
那么您知道去文件导入了
chosen maven and then chosen the project
选择行家，然后选择项目
but this is far simpler and the result
但这要简单得多，结果
is we have a project in our IDE and this
我们在IDE中有一个项目吗
is again this is not necessarily a new
再次这不一定是新的
feature instead of a spring tool suite
功能而不是 spring tool suite
for it's just very convenient to have
因为这很方便
all the stuff here and we're just going
这里所有的东西，我们就去
to create a simple application with a
用一个创建一个简单的应用程序
simple rest in point so class readings
简单的休息，以便课堂阅读
rest controller and the rest controller
休息控制器和休息控制器
will have a single end point get mapping
将有一个端点获取映射
a high string high
高弦高
and we'll return hello right so here's
我们会回去打招呼的，所以这是
our at-rest controller and I'll import
我们的休息控制器，我将导入
the right types make sure that's all
正确的类型可以确保所有这些
here yeah good all right and we're gonna
是的，很好，我们要
run this and this is again this will
运行这个，这又是这个
launch application in the IDE and it'll
在IDE中启动应用程序，它将
contribute it to our spring boot
为我们的 spring boot 贡献力量
dashboard this is also another one of
仪表板这也是另一个
the all-time my one of my all-time
我所有的时间之一
favorite features of the spring tooling
弹簧工具最喜欢的功能
here for Eclipse and for any ID and in
在这里用于Eclipse和任何ID，并在
general is this spring boot dashboard
一般是这个 spring boot 仪表板
this dashboard gives me a single at a
这个仪表板给我一个
glance view of all the things that are
一览所有事物
all the applications I'm working with or
我正在使用的所有应用程序或
whether they're in the same multi module
他们是否在同一个多模块中
maven build or not I can see them all
是否行家，我都能看到他们
here this will even show me you know let
这甚至会告诉我你知道让
me install a run spring cloud services
我安装运行Spring Cloud Services
like the Eureka service registry you
像Eureka服务注册表一样
know the config server the zip gain etc
知道配置服务器的压缩增益等
I can just click on this button and and
我可以单击此按钮，然后
get those available and I can launch
得到那些，我可以启动
them if I need to if it makes it very
他们，如果我需要的话
simple to simulate a working sort of
简单地模拟一种工作方式
Microsoft environment my local machine
Microsoft环境我的本地计算机
so we've got the application we've got
所以我们有了应用程序
it running and you notice that the first
它正在运行，您会注意到第一个
thing that happens when you run the
当您运行时发生的事情
application is that the the annotations
应用是注释
for the application itself become
因为应用程序本身成为
highlighted right you can see there's a
突出显示的右侧，您可以看到有一个
little spring boot badge and the and the
小弹簧靴徽章和
gutter there and the components that are
那里的装订线和
in play for the application are you know
您正在为该应用程序玩吗
augmented with this extra information
补充了这些额外的信息
that you can see when you hover over the
当您将鼠标悬停在
annotation so this risk controller
注释，因此此风险控制者
annotation is highlighted that means
注释突出显示，这意味着
that the actor the controller is in play
控制器正在扮演的演员
we can see that we can confirm as much
我们可以看到我们可以确认
by looking at the properties here in
通过查看这里的属性
this spring boot dashboard and you'll
这个 spring boot 仪表板，您将
notice that we've got a lot of
请注意，我们有很多
information here we've got the request
信息在这里，我们有要求
mappings in point this shows me
点映射显示了我
for example the input that I contributed
例如我贡献的投入
this is static analysis so this is
这是静态分析，所以这是
actually information that's being drawn
实际上是正在绘制的信息
from the source code of the application
从应用程序的源代码
itself at at design time right there's
本身在设计时就存在
not necessarily any runtime contingent
不一定有任何运行时条件
yet there is this beans in point though
然而虽然有这个豆
and this beans in point is thoroughly
这个豆是彻底的
and completely based on runtime
完全基于运行时
information based on information that
信息基于
we're getting from the actuator that
我们从执行器得到
we're then able to service here so if I
这样我们就可以在这里服务，如果我
go to
去
the search field here I can see that
在这里的搜索字段中，我可以看到
I've got a recruiting dress controller
我有一个招募的服装主管
and there's in this code page it has no
在此代码页中没有
dependencies right now and it's not
依赖关系，现在不是
injected into anything so that
注入任何东西，以便
information is being provided at runtime
在运行时提供信息
if you look if you mouse over all of
如果您查看是否将鼠标悬停在所有
this you can see what process this this
这个你可以看到这个过程
endpoint is running in and you can see
端点正在运行，您可以看到
where to go to actually hit that end
到底要去哪里
point I get that again is information
我再次得到的是信息
that we're getting at runtime not at
我们在运行时得到的不是
compile time so you'll see that one big
编译时间，这样一来，
feature here in spring tool suite is
Spring工具套件中的功能是
that were doing a lot more to augment
在增加方面做得更多
your experience while you know while
你的经历而你知道
working with the the code at runtime and
在运行时使用代码并
that's that's a very very useful thing
那是非常非常有用的东西
to do I think it provides a lot of
我认为它提供了很多
information that you couldn't reasonably
您无法合理理解的信息
expect to mine from the source code
希望从源代码中挖掘
alone otherwise you'd have to create a
一个人，否则你必须创建一个
complete model of what spring boot
弹簧靴的完整模型
itself is doing right and that gets to
本身做得正确，并且可以
our next the next thing that I really
我们接下来的下一件事，我真的
like about this is that they've moved
就像这是因为他们已经搬家了
aside some of the tooling that was
除了一些工具
designed to support more static
设计用于支持更多静态
deterministic sort of xml based
基于xml的确定性排序
Springwood applications it's still
Springwood应用仍然
installable if you want as an extra
如果您需要额外安装
thing but it's it's nice that it's not
的东西，但不是
here by default because you don't get
默认情况下在这里，因为您不会
any false positives one thing that I
任何误报我一件事
struggle with in any idea especially the
与任何想法斗争，特别是
more modern IDs like like Eclipse and
更现代的ID，例如Eclipse和
and you know the intelligent support
而且您知道智能支持
NetBeans and so on is that they have
NetBeans等是它们具有
that are trying to model all of what
试图建模所有的东西
spring is trying to do and they create
春天试图做，他们创造
this feedback this validation in the
该反馈在
code itself but most of the time it's a
代码本身，但大多数情况下是
false positive there's errors there that
假阳性那里有错误
dish that just simply aren't so the code
只是根本不是这样的菜
runs just fine it compiles just fine and
运行得很好，编译也很好，
you end up having to disable that here
你最终不得不在这里禁用它
we're not having you yet we have just
我们还没有你，我们只有
working code it's green it's clean it
工作代码，绿色，干净
works and I'm not being hounded by all
工作，我并没有被所有人束缚
these errors and quick fixes that don't
这些错误和快速修复
really apply so that's very very nice we
真的适用，所以我们非常非常高兴
have now a very simple application let's
现在有一个非常简单的应用程序，让我们
let's see if we can go further well
让我们看看我们能否走得更好
first of all I can use control 6 this is
首先，我可以使用控件6
the navigation for symbols in the in the
中的符号导航
current code page and that shows me also
当前的代码页，这也向我显示
I can navigate you know I can see that I
我可以导航你知道我可以看到我
have the high end point I can go to that
有我可以去的高端点
if I hit control 6 again I am you know I
如果我再次击中控制键6我就是你知道我
can hit it again while I'm engaged so I
我订婚时可以再次击中它，所以我
hit control 6 then hit control sticks
击中控制6然后击中控制杆
again and that shows me the navigate
再次向我展示了导航
navigation options for the current
当前的导航选项
workspace as opposed to just the current
工作空间而不是当前
code page in this case says I've only
在这种情况下的代码页说我只
got one code page and they're on the
只有一个代码页，它们位于
same file they are Bay
他们是海湾相同的文件
one of the same but it is nice to know
其中之一，但很高兴知道
you've got these options another thing
你还有这些选择
that's really convenient here is when
那真的很方便
you navigate these different annotations
您浏览这些不同的注释
you can see what they're composed of so
你可以看到它们的组成
the spring bootie application is itself
spring bootie应用程序本身
a spring book configuration which is
弹簧书的配置是
itself a configuration which is itself a
本身就是一个配置
component right you can see that rest
组件正确，您可以看到其余部分
controller is internal controller and a
控制器是内部控制器，
components all this stuff you know it
组成所有这些你知道的东西
this is the composed annotation composed
这是组成的注释
mid annotation that spring season
春季的中期注释
runtime that's what leads to spring
运行时才是导致春天的原因
honoring you know certain contracts or
尊重您知道某些合同或
certain obligations right it knows that
它知道某些义务
rest controller is both controller and a
休息控制器既是控制器又是控制器
component or rather a controller is a
组件，或者说控制器是一个
component so it knows all that and it's
组件，所以它知道所有这些，而且
able to to do certain things for us but
能够为我们做某些事情，但是
if you're staring at the code it's not
如果您盯着代码，那不是
in - it's not it may not be immediately
在-不是，可能不是立即
intuitive that this is working because
直观地知道这是有效的，因为
it is it is itself a stereotyped
它本身就是刻板印象
annotation so to get that feedback here
注释，以便在此处获得反馈
is super convenient now we did control 6
超级方便，现在我们控制了6
twice if we do it if we then do forward
如果我们再做一次的话，再做两次
slash forward slash in the control 6
控件中的正斜杠6
navigation option we get runtime
导航选项，我们获得运行时
information so what you just saw there
信息，所以你刚才在那看到的
before was static analysis but here we
以前是静态分析，但在这里我们
get runtime information we get
获取我们获得的运行时信息
information about which endpoints are
有关哪些端点的信息
exposed in the application mind if we
如果我们暴露在应用程序的思想
click on one for example it opens up the
单击一个，例如，它打开了
web browser and shows me the the input
网络浏览器，并向我显示输入
right so that's very very convenient now
对，所以现在非常方便
I've got a simple example here I've got
我这里有一个简单的例子
a simple endpoint let's I want to
一个简单的端点，让我想
parameterize this one I can create a
参数化这个我可以创建一个
property that I can then contribute to
我可以贡献的财产
the rest controller so let's open up the
其余的控制器，所以让我们打开
application app properties file this is
应用程序应用程序属性文件，这是
the you know the default place to find
您知道要查找的默认位置
configuration for spring boot
弹簧靴的配置
applications and so we're gonna create a
应用程序，因此我们将创建一个
new meetings name property right so
新会议的名称属性正确
we're gonna say greetings name equals
我们要说问候名字等于
world now you notice that first of all
现在的世界，您首先注意到
get dev tools running in the background
使开发工具在后台运行
so it's just live reloading everything
这样就可以实时重新加载所有内容
the time I hit save on anything it's
我击中保存任何东西的时间
giving me analysis it's showing me that
给我分析表明我
this property doesn't exist it's not in
此属性不存在，不在
any of the configuration property
任何配置属性
metadata in the entire class path so it
整个类路径中的元数据，因此
knows that this isn't you know there's
知道这不是你知道的
no configuration properties POJO that
没有配置属性POJO
has this property in it
具有此属性
it's still valid so it's yellow not red
它仍然有效，所以黄色而不是红色
but it's still you know it's trying to
但是你仍然知道它在努力
it's trying to give us a clue that we
试图给我们一个线索，我们
can do better so let's see if we can fix
可以做得更好，让我们看看是否可以解决
things here greetings properties and
这里的东西问候属性和
we'll make this a configuration
我们将其配置
properties greetings
属性问候
private string name and we'll use
私有字符串名称，我们将使用
control one and generate some getters
控制一个并产生一些吸气剂
and setters and enable configuration
和设置器并启用配置
properties so amiable configuration
属性如此友好的配置
properties
属性
greetings properties dot class and we
问候属性点类，我们
opened up this property file and there
打开这个属性文件，在那里
it is now if you go back to application
现在，如果您返回应用程序
of properties it's immediately aware of
立即知道的属性
the fact that we've now fixed it it can
我们现在已经修复它的事实可以
give us hover information and so on and
给我们悬停信息等等
that's an align with what it does for
这与其用途是一致的
everything else if you do server that
其他一切，如果你做服务器
port equals eighty ten for example
例如，端口等于八十
you'll see that it's it knows what port
您会看到它知道哪个端口
it is it knows what you know knows mitad
是的，它知道你知道的东西
the documentation for that essentially
本质上的文档
it gives us a lot of feedback in the in
它给了我们很多反馈
the tool immediately right so now I've
该工具马上就可以了，现在我已经
got this M rest controller we can see
有了这个M控制器，我们可以看到
that the rest controller is not used if
如果不使用rest控制器
you scroll down here you can show it's
您在此处向下滚动可以显示
running in this process and it's not
在这个过程中运行，它不是
injected into anything else
注入其他任何东西
right if you go to our rest controller
对，如果你去我们的休息管理员
that's inject now the let's inject now
现在注入，让我们现在注入
the greetings properties so meetings
问候属性，因此会议
properties P P and we're going to
属性PP，我们将
generate a constructor here using that
在这里生成一个构造函数
field alright good so there's that and
很好，所以有
when I do that I'm going to say hello
当我这样做的时候我会打招呼
this GP get name and all we start at the
这个GP得了名字，我们从
endpoint and now as soon as I do that I
终结点，现在我就这样做了
can see the
可以看到
application itself the beam itself
光束本身
injects you know I can see that this is
注射你知道我可以看到这是
based on runtime information of course I
根据课程I的运行时信息
can see that that beam injects the
可以看到光束注入了
Greenes properties here and it's in this
在这里绿化属性，就在此
hover again that's runtime information
再次悬停，这是运行时信息
sort of seamlessly blended with static
与静态无缝融合的一种
analysis and so on feedback that we're
分析等反馈
that we're getting here and it's
我们到达这里，这是
augmented so you still got some you've
增强，所以你仍然有一些
got a useful result if you don't have
如果没有的话，会得到有用的结果
this code running you know it's not it's
运行此代码，您知道不是
not wrong but when you run the
没错，但是当您运行
application it can give you so much more
应用程序可以为您提供更多
information including for example which
信息包括例如
beans are related to which so this is a
豆与之相关，所以这是一个
different view I think of of the
我想到的不同观点
information that we would have gotten
我们将获得的信息
here and there and the properties view
在这里和那里以及属性视图
right so request mappings beans general
对，因此请求映射bean一般
now one thing that can be daunting for
现在，一件事可能令人生畏
spring boot you you know new spring boot
spring boot ，你知道新的 spring boot
users its figure out which object
用户找出哪个对象
supplier which objects are in play at
供应商哪些对象在起作用
one time so as you may know in spring
如你所知春季
boot whether you can conditionally
引导您是否可以有条件
create or contribute objects to the
创建或贡献对象
object graph using the conditional
使用条件的对象图
annotations and any other annotations
注释和任何其他注释
that are men and a meta annotated with
那是男人和一个元注释
conditional so lets them let's make this
有条件的，让他们让我们做这个
bean this greenish properties object or
将此绿色属性对象置为bean或
rather let's make this this a rest
宁愿我们休息一下
controller up conditional so we're gonna
有条件的控制器，所以我们要
make this conditioner we're gonna say
做这个护发素，我们要说
conditional on oh I don't know class so
有条件哦，我不懂课
if the class Java dot Lang that string
如果类Java点郎那个字符串
is on the class path then this bean will
在类路径上，那么这个bean将
be registered it'll be contribute so you
被注册，将有助于您
can see that it's highlighted when the
可以看到，当
one application we started it's
我们启动的一个应用是
highlighted the bean is obviously there
突出显示豆显然在那里
because the class traveling string
因为班上的旅行字符串
exists and it shows us the results of
存在，它向我们展示了
that condition so we know that this this
这种情况，所以我们知道
bean is running in the process ID 1401 v
bean在进程ID 1401 v中运行
we can see that it's called this and so
我们可以看到它叫做
on everything is as we expect if we
一切都如我们所期望的
change this condition again to name
再次将此条件更改为名称
equals java.lang foo of course that
当然等于java.lang foo
doesn't exist where we start and now you
我们开始的地方不存在，现在您
can see that that mean the rest
可以看到那意味着剩下的
controller is no longer highlighted
控制器不再突出显示
right it's showing that this bean is not
对，这表明这个豆不是
present at runtime
在运行时出现
and then we can confirm that again by
然后我们可以通过再次确认
going to control six control six four
要控制六控制六四
slash
削减
and looking for high right high doesn't
而寻找高右高不会
exist anymore it's not in the run time
不再存在，它不在运行时
graph
图形
this a run time feedback this analysis
这是运行时反馈此分析
of what's happening and what's what's
发生了什么，什么是什么
you know actually in play this can make
你知道这实际上可以使
it very easy to debug things for example
例如，调试东西非常容易
so let's say if I remove this comment
所以说如果我删除此评论
that out it'll restart itself and
它将重新启动自己，
everything will be back to as we expect
一切都会恢复到我们所期望的
and I've got an application here I want
我这里有一个应用程序
to move this application to the cloud so
将此应用程序移动到云中
what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna go to my
我要做的是我要去我的
file system here and I'll create a new
文件系统，我将创建一个新的
file and the file will be a Cloud
文件，该文件将是云
Foundry manifest yamo right so manifest
铸造清单yamo如此明显
dot y mo and the pending manifest is a
点y mo和待处理的清单是
very simple document doesn't have to
非常简单的文档不必
have all that much you can give it a
有那么多你可以给它一个
name for example and so I'll just call
例如名字，所以我就打电话
this STS live demo okay and you can do
这个STS现场演示很好，您可以
all sorts of other things here you could
您还可以在这里进行其他各种操作
you know you can see that there's
你知道你可以看到
tooling here that supports this manifest
支持此清单的工具
file this is a yam oh right it's a yam
文件，这是一个山药哦，对，这是一个山药
will file but it's also a crowdfunding
会提出申请，但这也是众筹
manifest and there's a particular set of
清单，并且有一组特定的
things you can put in this file and so
您可以放入此文件中的内容等等
this is actually supported by tooling
这实际上是由工具支持的
that we have here in spring tool suite
在Spring工具套件中
so we could specify everything else here
所以我们可以在这里指定其他所有内容
for example memory and all that stuff
例如记忆和所有这些东西
but for our purposes and the it suffice
但就我们的目的而言，就足够了
it to leave it as it is so what leads
它离开它，所以导致
out there and then we can actually now
在那里，然后我们实际上可以现在
deploy this to crowdfunding so I'm gonna
部署到众筹，所以我要
do just that all add cloud find users
只需添加云即可找到用户
target I'll log in I'll say Starbucks
目标我要登录我会说星巴克
man
男人
all right and we'll hit select space
好的，我们将点击选择空间
it's gonna ask me to select a an
会问我选择一个
organization and a space I'll choose
组织和我要选择的空间
that from Eng hit finish finish again
来自Eng的影片再次完成
and that's going to take a few seconds
这将需要几秒钟
here to connect to the platform interact
这里连接平台互动
with it authenticate do all that kind of
使用它进行所有此类身份验证
stuff you can see it's trying to you
你可以看到它正在尝试你的东西
know trying to fetch all the app
知道尝试获取所有应用程序
instances there we are so we have a
实例，我们在那里，所以我们有一个
whole bunch of services and applications
整个服务和应用程序
that are available to us and we can now
可供我们使用，现在我们可以
deploy our application so I'll delete
部署我们的应用程序，以便删除
this existing one goodbye right so I can
现有的再见，所以我可以
do anything I would do from the command
做我将要执行的命令
line we're gonna do it from here as well
行，我们也将从这里开始
and we're gonna do they want to take
而且我们要他们采取
this demo and I'll just deployed just
这个演示，我只是部署
drag and drop and it'll prompt me to say
拖放它会提示我说
I want to deploy this application using
我想使用
the manifest file that you've just
您刚刚的清单文件
created and it's detected we'll give it
创建并检测到我们将给它
a demo here a name and it'll have
一个演示在这里的名字，它将有
everything it needs to build a sort of a
它需要建立一切的一切
hydrate that definition and expand it
水合该定义并扩展它
into a an application and so on it'll be
进入应用程序，依此类推
able to do I think it needs to run that
能够做到，我认为它需要运行
application correctly so it's gonna look
正确的应用程序，它将看起来
at the application is gonna push it the
在应用程序将推动它
platform is gonna see the incoming
平台将看到传入
artifact it's going to understand that
神器，它将了解
it's a java application a jar it's going
这是一个Java应用程序，它正在运行
to create a file system that has
创建具有以下内容的文件系统
everything needed to run that
运行该程序所需的一切
application including a jdk or rather a
包括jdk或
JRE if we were using Tomcat it would
如果我们使用的是Tomcat，它将使用JRE
have a you know if we had to put a dot
你知道我们是否必须加点
war it would have downloaded a patchy
战争，它会下载一个补丁
Tomcat latest and greatest to install of
Tomcat最新，最强大的安装
that and then run that for us for
然后为我们运行
example so it's gonna do all that stuff
例子，所以它将做所有的事情
for us C must be seamlessly behind the
对我们而言，C必须无缝地位于
scenes we get to see all that reflected
我们可以看到所有反映的场景
here in the console right so again we've
在控制台中，所以我们再次
managed to source or originate a new
设法获取或发起新的
project edit it get lots of feedback
项目编辑得到很多反馈
while we're developing it and editing
在我们开发和编辑时
and live in the ID without ever having
并一直住在ID中
to leave we can open up the endpoints
离开我们可以打开端点
and so on we could make changes to it we
等等，我们可以对其进行更改
could then package it up for a platform
然后可以将其打包为平台
like Cloud Foundry get smart feedback
像Cloud Foundry一样获得明智的反馈
there and then seamlessly all within the
在那里，然后无缝地
tooling drag deploy it to a platform
工具拖动将其部署到平台
right so this is a very nice experience
对，所以这是一个非常不错的体验
right this gives you the ability to move
对，这使您能够移动
quickly from concept all the way to a
从概念迅速发展到
customer which is at the end of the day
一天结束时的客户
what we want and you at every step of
我们想要的以及您的每一步
the way we've
我们的方式
gotten help now in a real more in a more
现在获得了更多的帮助
production sort of a example obviously I
生产样例显然我
would I'd have a continuous integration
我会不断整合吗
pipeline and so there is new support for
管道，因此有新的支持
concourse concourse C is our is the
大堂大堂C是我们的
pivotal sort of post converged
关键的岗位融合
infrastructure post you know post
您知道的基础设施职位
regular CI kind of tool it's a it's a
常规CI工具，这是一个
tool designed to handle the continuous
设计用于处理连续性的工具
integration and distribution and
整合与分配
deployment of distributed systems not
不部署分布式系统
just individual monolithic applications
只是个别的整体应用
and there's a you know there's a yeah mo
还有一个你知道那里是一个莫
config file for that as well and there's
的配置文件，以及
a there's tooling for that as well so
那里也有工具
it's a very natural thing so didn't then
这是很自然的事情，所以没有
say I wanted to play this to concourse
说我想玩这个玩
so there we go there's our application
所以我们去那里有我们的应用程序
it's up and running we can see that here
它已经启动并运行了，我们可以在这里看到
right we have all this information that
对，我们拥有所有这些信息
we have a you know about the application
我们对您有了解
we can open it up in the web browser
我们可以在网络浏览器中打开它
here there's our application running
这是我们的应用程序正在运行
alive on on Cloud Foundry I'll hit hi
在Cloud Foundry上还活着，我打个招呼
and it says hello world right so we've
它说你好世界，所以我们已经
managed to deploy application make
设法部署应用程序
changes to it we can see the logs for
更改它，我们可以查看以下日志
the application all within the ID now
现在该应用程序全部在ID中
this is just you know this is all very
这就是你知道这一切非常
useful in of itself it's a faster more
本身很有用，速度更快
svelte more more more efficient
更苗条更有效
springing tool suite experience you get
不断涌现的工具套件体验
a lot more useful information as opposed
与之相反，更多有用的信息
to noise you know the signal-to-noise
噪声，您知道信噪比
here is much better at much more in our
这比我们的要好得多
favor but and if that were all that
恩，但是如果那一切
would be a very interesting very very
将会非常有趣
powerful release and I'm certainly happy
强大的发布，我当然很高兴
I'm happy I upgraded but this is a one
我很高兴升级，但这是一个
thing we haven't really talked about
我们还没有真正谈论过的事情
which is that all the tooling that we've
这就是我们拥有的所有工具
looked at here so so far the the
到目前为止看着这里
improved runtime metadata the the the
改进的运行时元数据
analysis that it's giving you the the
分析，它给你
insight for you know the support for
洞察力为您所知
Cloud Foundry the manifest for concourse
Cloud Foundry的清单清单
all of that stuff is based on something
所有这些东西都是基于某种东西
called a language server which is a
称为语言服务器
protocol that originated in Microsoft's
源自Microsoft的协议
Visual Studio code open source project
Visual Studio代码开源项目
language servers are just a protocol
语言服务器只是一个协议
it's a it's a separate process that runs
这是一个独立的流程
out adjacent to the the tool the ID and
与工具相邻的ID和
that analyzes code for you and there's a
为您分析代码，并且有一个
interaction between the ID and the
ID与
language server that interaction is IDE
交互是IDE的语言服务器
agnostic and so while it started with
不可知的，所以虽然它始于
Visual Studio code other IDs have
其他ID具有的Visual Studio代码
started to implement that so spring tool
开始实施那个弹簧工具
suite is now using those language
套件现在正在使用这些语言
servers but those language servers are
服务器，但那些语言服务器是
all
所有
available for other ideas also uh you
也可用于其他想法
can use it in Visual Studio code you can
可以在Visual Studio代码中使用它
use it in spring tool suite you can use
可以在spring工具套件中使用它
it an atom and I I hear you know from
它是一个原子，我听到你从
what I saw there's people looking at
我看到的是有人在看
implementing it for Emacs I mean you
为Emacs实现它，我的意思是你
know the sky's the limit really so right
真的知道天空是极限
now there's a real studio code and atom
现在有一个真正的工作室代码和原子
and obviously the spring tool suite
显然是 spring tool suite
support so let's look at the same
支持，让我们来看看
project that we just created inside of
我们刚刚在其中创建的项目
videos to decode so I'm going to go to
要解码的视频，所以我要转到
this project this is the same one that
这个项目是那个
we were just in right so if we go here
我们就在正确的地方，所以如果我们去这里
you can see it says home Geelong
你可以看到它说回家吉朗
document test yes for demo there go here
文档测试是演示的，去这里
home to your long documents this to us
您的长文件的所在地
for demo I'm gonna run the application
对于演示，我将运行该应用程序
I'll hit code now remember the language
我会打代码，现在要记住语言
server is a separate process it's a
服务器是一个单独的过程
thing that's running independent of any
独立于任何事物而运行的事物
particular tool and so if I open up this
特定的工具，所以如果我打开这个
code because it's running inside of a
代码，因为它在一个
spring tool suite you can see that after
spring tool suite ，您可以看到
a second it gets the same runtime
一秒钟它获得相同的运行时间
metadata right I can see all the
我可以看到所有的元数据
information that I could see inside of a
我可以在里面看到的信息
spring tool suite here when I mouse over
鼠标悬停在这里时， spring tool suite
these these different hovers right so if
这些这些不同的徘徊，所以如果
I if I am mouse over I get the same
如果我将鼠标悬停在上面，我会得到相同的结果
information I can navigate using control
我可以使用控件导航的信息
P and that allows me to look at
P，那让我看看
different code pages for example if I do
不同的代码页，例如，如果我这样做
at it'll show me static analysis it'll
会告诉我静态分析
show me for example the the annotations
给我看看例如注释
they're just saw before that rest
他们只是在休息之前就被看到了
controller is composed of controller
控制器由控制器组成
controller and component it'll show me
控制器和组件，它将向我显示
the static analysis ethically now
现在进行符合道德的静态分析
analyzed high end point as well right so
也分析了高端点，所以
I get all that just like I did before
我得到的一切就像以前一样
there's also controlled T and ctrl T if
如果还有T和Ctrl T，
I do a four slash you know you know hash
我做一个四斜杠，你知道你知道哈希
tag for slash forward slash I can see
可以看到斜杠的标记正斜杠
the runtime augmented view of all the
所有的运行时扩充视图
endpoints just as before as well so I
端点也一样，所以我
can click on that and it opens up opened
可以单击它并打开打开
up the browser showing me the endpoint
浏览器显示端点
then it that is running right now now of
然后它现在正在运行
course in this case I've run the
当然，在这种情况下，我已经运行了
application in spring tools okay so
在弹簧工具中的应用还可以
let's go ahead and shut that down here
让我们继续并在这里关闭它
and then just return here and you'll
然后回到这里，你会
appreciate also that you can run things
也欣赏您可以运行的东西
inside of vs code right so if I hit if I
在vs代码内部，所以如果我点击
hit hit run and it'll create a run
点击运行，它将创建一个运行
configuration and the first time it does
配置和第一次
that it creates a configuration but it
它创建了一个配置，但它
doesn't necessarily launch it so yeah
不一定会启动它，是的
to do a five again in this case and
在这种情况下再做一次五
there we go so now it's gonna actually
我们去了，所以现在
launch the application inside of Visual
在Visual内部启动应用程序
Studio code we're using the same
我们使用的Studio代码相同
debugger that's you know that Microsoft
您知道Microsoft的调试器
contributed to the Visual Studio code
贡献给Visual Studio代码
the same machinery so all that is
相同的机器，所以这就是
working it's a very very sophisticated
工作非常复杂
bugger right you not know I'm not sure
虫虫吧，你不知道我不确定
it's quite as far along as the one
它与一个
inside of Eclipse but very very very
在Eclipse中，但是非常非常非常
useful very functional sort of support
有用的非常实用的支持
now one thing to keep in mind here is
现在要记住的一件事是
that the sum total of what everything
那一切的总和
that you're using here in Visual Studio
您在Visual Studio中使用的位置
code is you know it's a very much an
代码是你知道这是一个非常
open source collaboration right the
开源协作
launcher slash debugger for Visual
用于Visual的启动器斜线调试器
Studio code was contributed by Microsoft
Studio代码由Microsoft提供
the Java language tooling itself by Red
Red语言本身的Java语言工具
Hat the spring boot and you know support
戴上弹簧靴，就知道了支持
and for for Cloud Foundry for Concours
对于Cloud Foundry for Concours
for for Bosh which is separate and for
为了波什这是分开的
spring boot itself all that is from
弹簧靴本身就是所有
pivotal so you know there's a lot of
关键的，所以你知道有很多
stuff coming together here seamlessly in
东西在这里无缝地融合在一起
a language that is how in a tooling
一种在工具中使用的语言
agnostic way and that's actually a one
不可知论的方式，那实际上是一种
of my really favorite features of Visual
我最喜欢的Visual功能
Studio code here is that I I'm I've got
我在这里的工作室代码是
pretty good Java support here I I'm not
我在这里不是很好的Java支持
quite sure if it's as far along as
我很确定它是否与
something like spring tool suite but I
像 spring tool suite ，但我
do have also very compelling support for
确实也对
dotnet for example all right so if
例如，dotnet可以，如果
you're in an enterprise where you've got
您所在的企业
you have to deal with both this is a
你必须处理这两个
nice option I can get a competent net
不错的选择，我可以得到一个能干的网
editor IDE here
在这里编辑IDE
I can do typescript for example which is
我可以做打字稿，例如
a language that Microsoft originated you
Microsoft起源于您的语言
know a lot of things I can do here all
我知道很多事情我可以在这里做
within one tool one ID and it's just the
在一个工具中只有一个ID，
same tooling same machinery same
相同的工具相同的机器
keystrokes and so on so we so we get a
击键等等，所以我们得到了一个
lot right we get a lot we got a lot from
好吧，我们得到了很多，我们得到了很多
the fact that this is now available
现在可以使用的事实
another other tools the spring tools
其他工具弹簧工具
page the spring i/o spring that i/o
春季I / O页面
tools page has been updated or sorry the
工具页面已更新或对不起
blog rather has been updated just today
博客今天才更新
to document the release of all the stuff
记录所有物品的释放
they knew the new features so if you
他们知道新功能，所以如果您
want to see more and you want to learn
想看更多，你想学习
how to install it
如何安装
you know from the different marketplaces
你知道来自不同的市场
and so on there's instructions here and
等等这里有指示
we encourage you to try the bit tuck
我们鼓励您尝试一点点
kick you know kick the tires and
踢你知道踢轮胎，
feedback we're always happy to have more
反馈，我们总是很乐意拥有更多
input and with that thanks so much for
输入，并非常感谢
watching and we'll see you next time
看，下次见
you
您